Hey, what are you doing?
おい、お前何してんの?
Hey?
なぁ?
What are you doing?
何 してんの?
Maybe he tried to escape to a Western-style mansion.
洋館に逃げようとしたもしかした
I don't know, that's it.
わかんじゃん、そんな
Yes, yes.
はい、 はい
What are you doing?
何やってんの?
I have all my luggage.
全部荷物持ってるやん
What is this?
これ何なの?
this.
これ
Are you licking me?
舐めてんの?
Sorry.
すいません
Huh?
あれ?
Are you licking me?
舐めてんの?
What should I do?
どうすんの?
Hey, okay.
おい、よしな
Lick it yourself.
自分で舐めていけ
I'll go.
行くよ
Yeah.
うん
Hey, Reka-chan, why did you fly?
おい、れかちゃん、お前何で飛んだの?
Sorry.
すいません
What do you mean?
どういうことなの?
I couldn't continue.
続けられなくて
What?
何が?
Are you licking me?
舐めてんの?
Well, no.
まあ、いいや
Should I send this photo to my mom?
お母さんにこうやって写真送ろっか
What?
な ぁ?
Please stop.
やめてください
What?
な ぁ?
Stop, look, this is a mirror.
やめてほら、これ、鏡
Let's have fun taking photos.
楽しく撮ろうや
Na
な
ah?
ぁ?
She said she didn't have a boyfriend.
彼 氏おらんって言っておったやん
What do you mean?
どういうことなの?
Eh?
えぇ?
Hey?
なぁ?
Should I send it to my boyfriend like this?
彼氏に送ろっか、こうやって
Please stop.
やめてください
Hey?
なぁ?
I'm your new boyfriend.
俺が新しい彼氏だよ
Should I take a picture?
撮ってろか
Eh?
え ぇ?
Hey?
なぁ?
Are you approaching me and my boyfriend?
俺と彼氏に近づいておらんのか
Look, aren't you approaching me and my boyfriend?
ほら、俺と彼氏に近づいておらんのか
Hey?
なぁ?
What should I do?
どうすんの?
Well, you're right.
まあ、お正気やな
Should I take a picture of this and sell it?
これ、撮影して販売しようか
Hey?
なぁ?
Yeah.
うん
If you don't like it, bring me 500,000 yen.
嫌やったら50万持ってこい
I paid 500,000 yen and bought the video from before,
50万払って、この前の動画買い取って、
Total from before this video.
この動画前から合計で
Hey?
なぁ?
Well, 500,000 is fine.
まあいいよ、50万でいいよ
Can you bring it?
持ってこれる?
That's impossible.
無理ですね
If you force it, 500,000 yen, just butter it up.
無理やったら50万、ただバター力しろよ
Sigh.
は ぁ
Easy to punish.
お仕置きやすい
What the heck, this skirt is nice.
なんなん、このスカート、いいよ
Okay, this is it.
いいじゃん、これ
If you like it, just say it.
好きなのに言ったらいい
I think I'm about to take it off.
もう、脱がそうか
I'm about to take it off.
もう、脱がそう
Skirt, what is this?
スカート、なにこれ?
Cute underwear.
可愛い、下着やん
Hey?
なぁ?
Okay, this.
いいやん、これ
Yeah.
うん
This is the best, this.
これ、最高やん、これ
These are cute underwear.
可愛い、下着ですね
It's so cute.
可愛いやん、めっちゃ
Hey, look this way.
なぁ、こっち向いて
It's so cute.
めっちゃ可愛いなぁ
It's really good.
めっちゃいいやん
What?
な ぁ?
Yeah.
うん
It's cute.
可愛いね
cold?
寒い?
Is it cold?
寒いの?
Should I send this to her?
彼女にこれ送ろっか
Oh, please stop.
え、やめてください
Hey?
なぁ?
I don't like it.
嫌です
Hey?
なぁ?
What should I do?
どうする?
Because it's cute.
せっかく可愛いからな
Shall we continue like this today?
今日はこのままはめよっか
Kozaki, let me go over your cock and put it in quickly.
小崎、チンポ越えさせて、さっさと入れて
Now you can touch my cock.
もう、俺のチンポも触れや
Yeah.
うん
This is an amazing drawing.
すごい絵図だね、これ
Kosaki, are you looking at my ears?
小崎、耳見てるの?
this.
これ
My hands are stuck.
手が止まってるぞ
I'll put it in.
入れしまうよ
There's a clue there.
そこに手つきや
I don't like it.
嫌です
What's up, Licca-chan?
どうなの、リカちゃん?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Look up properly.
ちゃんと顔上げて
You can make fun of Mr. Kozaki's parts.
小崎さんのパーツばかしていいぞ
Because it was difficult to do.
やりづらかったから
Is this the way it is?
このままですか?
That's fine.
いいです
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Yeah.
うん
I'll do my best to follow you.
頑張ってついてやるよ
Ah, that hurts.
あー、痛い
Go to work properly.
ちゃんと出勤しろよ
yes.
はい
Did you understand?
分かったんか?
Don't make me angry.
あんま俺を怒らすんじゃないぞ
yes.
はい
What are you doing?
何やでくんだよ
How do you answer?
なんと答える?
I'll go to work properly.
ちゃんと出勤します
Then I'll go home.
じゃあ俺帰るから
yes.
はい
Come tomorrow.
明日来いよ
good job.
お疲れ様
thank you for your hard work.
お疲れ様です
yes.
はい